Baruch, Ismar Compilation of U.S. Employment Service and U.S. Civil Service Documents 6099
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Federal Salary Classification in Alaska., 1941 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  National Federation of Federal Employees, Local no.251. Federal salary classification in Alaska. Juneau, 1941.
- Classification Training Courses., 1939-1943 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Classification Training Courses., 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Personnel classification division memoranda (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Spine title: P.C. Division Memos No. 2-75
- Personnel classification division memoranda (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Spine title: Division Memos Nos. 76-182 --- Sixth volume: nos.183-202 missing.
- Federal Salary Data to 1933, 1789-1933 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Salaries and distribution of 396,513 regular, full-time, permanent positions in the federal service on January 31, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Spine title: Federal Salary Data - January 31, 1937
- Personnel classification division memoranda, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Spine title: Memorandum No. 9 -- 1934
- Personnel classification division memoranda, 1932-1934 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Spine title: Memorandum Nos. 1 to 9 -- 1932- 34
- Notes of training courses PCD / Personnel Classification Division., 1941 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Spine title: P.C.D. Training Conference Notes 1941
- Salary Advancement Plan., 1939-1941 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Pay Legislation Survey, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  A partial survey of pay legislation, Field Section, Personnel Classification Division, April 1943.
- Personnel Classification Division. Manuals A2-A4., 1941-1946 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Personnel Classification Division. Manuals B1-D1., 1939-1945 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Personnel Classification Division. Manuals F1-G17., 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Personnel Classification Division. Manuals., 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Personnel Classification Division. Manuals., 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Personnel Classification Division. Manuals., 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  v.1. Copy 2.
- Personnel Classification Division. Manuals., 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  v.2. Copy 2.
- Personnel Classification Division. Manuals., 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Class Specifications., 1940 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Positions in the field service of the Farm Security Administration.
- Interdepartmental Classification Survey., 1944 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Revision of Personnel Classification Division procedures.
- Job-Load Analysis and Planning of Executive Work in National Forest Administration., 1932 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Manual for Forest Service officers by E. W. Lovridge.
- Navy Wage Schedules and Regulations., 1923-1940 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Papers on Hazard Pay Study., 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Personnel Classification Division. Trainee Handbook., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Training course in the basic principles and techniques of position classification.
- Position Classification Analysis., 1939 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Adapted to Home Owners Loan Corporation requitements by Ismar Baruch, Janyary 3, 1939.
- Q.M. Classification Manual., 1941 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  War Department.
- Supergrade Story., 1949-1952 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  v.1. Memoranda, letters, executive orders, documents.
- Supergrade Story., 1949-1952 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  v.2. Memoranda, letters, executive orders, documents.
- War Department. Wage Administration Manuals., 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- War Department. Wage Administration Manuals., 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Civil Service Law Briefs., 1926-1940 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  v.1. U.S. Court of Appeals in the District of Columbia.
- Civil Service Law Briefs., 1926-1940 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  v.2. Miscellaneous documents.
- Five Day Week Report., 1932-1938 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Papers in re report to the President on the five-day week.
- Government Corporations (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Service in government corporations; its status under the Retirement Act and the Civil Service Act and Rules.
- Hours and Overtime., 1930-1930 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Clippings, manuscripts, extracts, documents.
- Law Memos. Exclusions., 1925-1941 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Law Memos. Exclusions., 1925-1933 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Law Memos. Miscellaneous., 1923-1935 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Law Memos. Retirement., 1935-1942 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Law Notes (Box 18, Folder 10)
- War Department. Wage Administration Manuals., 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Law Memos. Miscellaneous., 1926-1941 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Law Memos. Miscellaneous., 1925-1941 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Personnel Positions and Organizations in the Federal Government, 1931-1942 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Personnel Positions and Organizations in the Federal Government, 1931-1942 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Personnel Positions and Organizations in the Federal Government, 1931-1942 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Public Personnel Administration, 1923-1924 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  v.1. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1923-1935 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  v.2. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1928-1935 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  v.3. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1930-1936 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  v.4. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1924-1937 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  v.5. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1935-1938 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  v.6. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1935-1938 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  v.7. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  v.8. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1938-1940 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  v.9. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1921-1940 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  v.10. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1932-1942 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  v.11. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  v.12. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1929-1942 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  v.13. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1922-1941 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  v.14. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1938-1942 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  v.15. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1919-1940 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  v.16. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1937-1947 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  v.17. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1939-1947 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  v.18. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1932-1947 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  v.19. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1939-1947 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  v.20. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1939-1947 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  v.21. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1939-1938 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  v.22. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1938-1947 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  v.23. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1938-1946 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  v.24. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Public Personnel Administration, 1940-1946 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  v.25. Articles, pamphlets, reports, and surveys on Federal, state, municipal, and foreign jurisdictions
- Removal and Reduction in Force, 1911-1935 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  v.1. Laws, regulations, memoranda, manuscript correspondence, notes.
- Removal and Reduction in Force, 1924-1936 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  v.2. Laws, regulations, memoranda, manuscript correspondence, notes.
- Removal and Reduction in Force, 1925-1937 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  v.3. Laws, regulations, memoranda, manuscript correspondence, notes.
- Removal and Reduction in Force, 1925-1941 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  v.4. Laws, regulations, memoranda, manuscript correspondence, notes.
- Removals. Official Documents, 1911-1930 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  Decisions, hearings, documents.
- Reorganization of the Executive Departments. Official Documents., 1923-1932 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- American University. Training Course., 1934-1935 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Public personnel administration. "In-service" training program, second semester, lectures by Leonard D. White, Luther Steward, Kenneth C. Vipond, L. J. O'Rourke, F. W. Brown, Ismar Baruch, William H. McReynolds, Lewis Meriam, James G. Yaden, Lewis H. Fisher, W. W. Stockberger.
- Reorganization of the Executive Departments. Official Documents., 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Residence and Domicile, 1909-1936 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  v.1. Notes, memoranda, and opinions regarding legal residence, etc.
- Residence and Domicile (Box 23, Folder 4)
  v.2. Notes, memoranda, and opinions regarding legal residence, etc.
- Retirement. Official Documents., 1924-1935 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  Hearings, documents, reports
- Training in the Public Service., 1935-1936 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  v.1. Pamphlets, reports, and papers. Includes 1935 Princeton University Conference, programs of the National Institute of Public Affairs, agency programs, 1931 University of Minnesota Conference, etc.
- Training in the Public Service., 1926-1937 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  v.2. Pamphlets, reports, and papers. Includes 1935 Princeton University Conference, programs of the National Institute of Public Affairs, agency programs, 1931 University of Minnesota Conference, etc.
- Training in the Public Service., 1937-1939 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  v.3. Pamphlets, reports, and papers. Includes 1935 Princeton University Conference, programs of the National Institute of Public Affairs, agency programs, 1931 University of Minnesota Conference, etc.
- Training in the Public Service., 1920-1939 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  v.4. Pamphlets, reports, and papers. Includes 1935 Princeton University Conference, programs of the National Institute of Public Affairs, agency programs, 1931 University of Minnesota Conference, etc.
- Training in the Public Service., 1930-1942 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  v.5. Pamphlets, reports, and papers. Includes 1935 Princeton University Conference, programs of the National Institute of Public Affairs, agency programs, 1931 University of Minnesota Conference, etc.
- Pamphlets on U.S. Civil Service., 1919-1939 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  v.1. Government agency publications, miscellaneous.
- Pamphlets on U.S. Civil Service., 1919-1941 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  v.2. Government agency publications, miscellaneous.
- Pamphlets on U.S. Civil Service., 1940-1943 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  v.3. Government agency publications, miscellaneous.
- Pamphlets on U.S. Civil Service., 1919-1944 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  v.4. Government agency publications, miscellaneous.
- Pamphlets on U.S. Civil Service., 1929-1944 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  v.5. Government agency publications, miscellaneous.
- Training in the Public Service., 1916-1940 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  v.6. Pamphlets, reports, and papers. Includes 1935 Princeton University Conference, programs of the National Institute of Public Affairs, agency programs, 1931 University of Minnesota Conference, etc.
- Training in the Public Service., 1923-1943 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  v.7. Pamphlets, reports, and papers. Includes 1935 Princeton University Conference, programs of the National Institute of Public Affairs, agency programs, 1931 University of Minnesota Conference, etc.
- Training in the Public Service., 1922-1941 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1882-1927 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  v.1. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1930-1934 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  v.2. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1924-1937 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  v.3. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1937-1938 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  v.4. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1882-1935 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  v.5. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1919-1938 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  v.6. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  v.7. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  v.8. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  v.9. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1937-1940 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  v.10. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1940-1944 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  v.11. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  v.12. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- Bureau of Efficiency. Reports and Circulars, 1924-1939 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  v.13. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1935-1943 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  v.14. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1939-1942 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  v.15. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  v.16. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1942-1944 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  v.17. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  v.18. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- U.S. Civil Service Papers, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  v.19. Compilation of papers, manuscripts, memoranda, clippings, letters, etc. on the Federal Civil Service.
- Veterans Preference., 1924-1939 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  Minutes, memoranda, letters, clippings, regulations, reports.
- Ismar Baruch Collection of Civil Service Papers - 1836-1953 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  The Pendleton Room, U.S. Civil Service Commission, February 1967
- Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada. Assembly Survey Questions., 1938 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Policies and practices survey; classification and pay plans
- Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada. Assembly Survey., 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  v.1. Policies and practices survey; classification and pay plans
- Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada. Assembly Survey., 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  v.2. Policies and practices survey; classification and pay plans
- Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada. Assembly Survey., 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  v.3. Policies and practices survey; classification and pay plans
- Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada. Assembly Survey., 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  v.4. Policies and practices survey; classification and pay plans
- Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada. Assembly Survey., 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  v.5. Policies and practices survey; classification and pay plans
- CSA Committee Papers, 1930-1942 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  v.1.
- CSA Committee Papers, 1929-1941 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  v.2.
- CSA Committee Papers, 1927-1939 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  v.3.
- Commission of Inquiry. Minutes of Evidence., 1934 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Commission of Inquiry on Public Service Personnel. Hearings held at the American Embassy, London, July 13-14, 1934.
- CSA Executive Council Minutes, 1934-1943 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- CSA Headquarters Reports, 1935-1942 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- CSA News Bulletins, 1928-1932 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- CSA Newsletter, 1935-1938 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  v.1-4
- CSA Newsletter, 1939-1942 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  v.5-8
- CSA Newsletter, 1943-1948 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  v.9-14
- CSA Pamphlets (Box 28, Folder 8)
- CSA Special Bulletins, 1936-1942 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Federal Personnel Board and Council of Personnel Administration., 1921-1933 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  Papers, clippings, documents
- Report on Rules. Classsification and Compensation Plans., 1931 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  Report of the technical committee on development, adoption, and administration of the classification and compensation plans and rules for the installation and administration of classification and compensation plans.
- Appendices, Report of the Personnel Policy Committee., 1948 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Hoover Commission
- Federal Laws., 1924-1939 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  General civil service and related legislation.
- Federal Personnel Conferences., 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  v.1. Includes various personnel organizations and professional groups.
- Federal Personnel Conferences., 1942-1943 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  v.3 (there is no v.2). Includes various personnel organizations and professional groups.
- Hoover Commission, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Hoover Commission, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Hoover Commission, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- National Civil Service Reform League. Publications., 1914-1934 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- National Civil Service Reform League. Publications., 1914-1941 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Proceedings of the National Civil Service Reform League., 1930-1939 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Federal Laws., 1940 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Federal Laws., 1941 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Federal Laws., 1942 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Federal Laws., 1943 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Federal Laws., 1944 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Federal Laws., 1945 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Federal Laws., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Federal Laws., 1947 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Federal Laws., 1948 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Federal Laws., 1949 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Official Documents., 1919-1935 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  Hearings and reports on civil service.
- Official Documents., 1923-1939 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Official Documents., 1931-1944 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Official Documents., 1937-1938 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Official Documents., 1939-1940 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Official Documents., 1939-1943 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Official Documents., 1941 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Public Laws., 1950 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Public Laws., 1951 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Public Laws., 1952 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Civil Service Bills, 1935-1937 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  74th Congress, 1st and 2nd Sessions, 75th Congress, 1st Session.
- Ellender Hearings., 1937-1940 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  Administration and operation of the civil service laws. Hearings before a special subcommittee, U.S. Senate, 76th Congress.
- Extracts from Hearings., 1939-1942 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  v.1. Independent Offices Appropriation hearings, and miscellaneous hearings.
- Extracts from Hearings., 1943-1946 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  v.2. Independent Offices Appropriation hearings, and miscellaneous hearings.
- Hearings on Sirovich Bill., 1935 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  "For improvement of the government service." Hearings, House of Representatives, Committee on the Civil Service, 74th Congress, 1st Session, on H.R.3980.
- Official Documents., 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Official Documents., 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Official Documents., 1945 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Official Documents., 1945 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Reports on Bills., 1937-1940 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  Grievances, leaves, and hours.
- Revised Hearings on H.R.3980., 1935 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  "For improvement of the government service." Hearings, House of Representatives, Committee on the Civil Service, 74th Congress, 1st Session. Robert Ramspeck, Chairman.
- C.I.T. Bulletins., 1933-1944 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  no.5-11. California Institute of Technology, Industrial Relations Section.
- Canada Classification Debates., 1919-1924 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Canada. Official Reports on Classification., 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1918-1940 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  v.2 (there is no v.1).
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1938-1940 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Hearings, Index, Reports. H.R.16, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Hearings. H.R.16, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  v.1. Investigation of civilian employment (Ramspeck hearings).
- Hearings. H.R.16, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  v.2. Investigation of civilian employment (Ramspeck hearings).
- Hearings. Independent Offices Appropriation., 1937 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Job Specifications. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  American Council on Education and Social Science Research Council. Includes directions for writing "records of usage."
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1921-1938 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  v.4
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1939-1947 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  v.5
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1942-1948 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  v.6
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1941-1947 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  v.7
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1926-1946 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  v.8
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1943-1951 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  v.9
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1938 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  v.10
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1923-1950 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  v.11
- Classification and Pay. Private Industry., 1947-1951 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  v.12
- Classification: State, City, and County., 1920-1932 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  Classification, salary standardization, personnel administration. Philadelphia, 1920; Spokane, 1926; Virginia, 1927; Milwaukee County, 1928; Ohio, 1929; New Jersey, 1930; Alabama, 1932.
- Employment Management in Industry., 1918-1932 (Box 35, Folder 2)